question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An atom contains a nucleus.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An average human can go two weeks without water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Celiac Disease is a disease that effects the heart, causing those effected to be unable to eat meat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Water always boils at 100&deg;C, 212&deg;F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A plant that has a life cycle for more than a year is known as an annual.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
